foreign
[Music]
corporate India Risk Index 2022
in today's world uncertainty is the norm
risk affects everyone from my division
[Music]
the company
two countries
in business every sector faces very risk
like changes in market conditions
cyber address
ES
risk is widespread
but is there a yardstick to measure it
so that it can be managed better there
are indices to measure various metrics
like air quality
average rainfalls
the magnitude of an earthquake
and even the distance to start
however measuring to what extent an
organization is exposed to and prepared
to manage risk is a challenging task
presenting icic and Lombard corporate
India Risk Index
[Music]
It's Kind comprehensive and standardized
corporate Risk Index so how is the
company's Risk Index calculated let's
take a look at company exponents
32 different parameters are measured
through a scientific process these are
segregated into risk exposure and risk
management
the parameters are then used to
understand the quantum operates being
faced by the company and its level of
preparedness to face this risks using a
wet cloth tool logic these parameters
are used to arrive at a risk of
with clear actionable areas various
companies would be in different
categories on the
other period just by company exports on
the corporate Risk Index care
a score of 60 suggests that company X
can optimally manage the risk it is
currently exposed to however managing
elements like competitive risk emerging
risk effectively will boost company
excess score
this can put in the superior risk
management category corporate India risk
intake is a key metric for companies
looking to managers
icic and Lombard corporate India Risk
Index intelligence partner crosstalk
[Music]